<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Eric Minwei Liu</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Eric Minwei Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 - 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>About I am a PhD student at Khurana lab led by Prof. Ekta Khurana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>Hui Shen, Juliann Shih, Daniel P Hollern, Linghua Wang, Reanne Bowlby, Satish K Tickoo, Vésteinn Thorsson, Andrew J Mungall, Yulia Newton, Apurva M Hegde, Joshua Armenia, Francisco Sánchez-Vega, John Pluta, Louise C Pyle, Rohit Mehra, Victor E Reuter, Guilherme Godoy, Jeffrey Jones, Carl S Shelley, Darren R Feldman, Daniel O Vidal, Davor Lessel, Tomislav Kulis, Flavio M Cárcano, Kristen M Leraas, Tara M Lichtenberg, Denise Brooks, Andrew D Cherniack, Juok Cho, David I Heiman, Katayoon Kasaian, Minwei Liu, Michael S Noble, Liu Xi, Hailei Zhang, Wanding Zhou, Jean C ZenKlusen, Carolyn M Hutter, Ina Felau, Jiashan Zhang, Nikolaus Schultz, Gad Getz, Matthew Meyerson, Joshua M Stuart, Rehan Akbani, David A Wheeler, Peter W Laird, Katherine L Nathanson, Victoria K Cortessis, Katherine A Hoadley, Cancer Genome Atlas Research Network “Integrated Molecular Characterization of Testicular Germ Cell Tumors”, Cell Reports, 23,3392-3406 (2018)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>