<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Eric Minwei Liu</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Eric Minwei Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; EML 2018 - 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>About I am currently a postdoctoral associate at Weill Cornell Medicine. I graduated from Weill Cornell Medicine with a PhD in Physiology, Biophysics and Systems Biology in 2019 under the supervision of Dr. Ekta Khurana. My research focuses on applying statistcal analysis and machine learning to large-scale multi-omics data in human cancers.
Email: mil2041 [at] med.cornell.edu
[Linkedin] [Google Scholar] [Github]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected projects</title>
      <link>/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/projects/</guid>
      <description>Non-coding cancer driver web app  Design a relational database system that stores the non-coding cancer evidences curated from literature.
 Develop a front-end web application that provides summary statistics and novel data representation of non-coding cancer evidences across 28 cancer types.  Cancer driver detection  Develop a new statistical inference method to discover coding and non-coding cancer drivers from 1962 whole -genome sequencing tumor samples. The package uses parallel programming to reduce the run time by 80%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>Matthew H Bailey, Collin Tokheim, Eduard Porta-Pardo, Sohini Sengupta, Denis Bertrand, Amila Weerasinghe, Antonio Colaprico, Michael C Wendl, Jaegil Kim, Brendan Reardon, Patrick Kwok-Shing Ng, Kang Jin Jeong, Song Cao, Zixing Wang, Jianjiong Gao, Qingsong Gao, Fang Wang, Eric Minwei Liu, Loris Mularoni, Carlota Rubio-Perez, Niranjan Nagarajan, Isidro Cortés-Ciriano, Daniel Cui Zhou, Wen-Wei Liang, Julian M Hess, Venkata D Yellapantula, David Tamborero, Abel Gonzalez-Perez, Chayaporn Suphavilai, Jia Yu Ko, Ekta Khurana, Peter J Park, Eliezer M Van Allen, Han Liang, Michael S Lawrence, Adam Godzik, Nuria Lopez-Bigas, Josh Stuart, David Wheeler, Gad Getz, Ken Chen, Alexander J Lazar, Gordon B Mills, Rachel Karchin, Li Ding, MC3 Working Group, Cancer Genome Atlas Research Network “Comprehensive Characterization of Cancer Driver Genes and Mutations”, Cell 173, 371–385.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Softwares</title>
      <link>/home/softwares/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/softwares/</guid>
      <description> CNCDatabase:  A full-stack database systems to organzie and query non-coding cancer driver evidences from literature.
 CNCDriver: Combined mutation recurrence and functional impact to identify coding and non-coding cancer drivers.
 netboxr:  an R package for integrative pathway analysis.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: mil2041 [at] med.cornell.edu
 413 E 69th Street Belfer Research Building New York, NY 10021
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>